# 哈喽 大家好 我是王刚
Hello, everybody. I'm Wang Gang.
# 现在我在江苏扬州
Now I'm in Yangzhou, Jiangsu Province.
# 然后这次过来可能一个星期吧
I will be here for a week this time.
# 就是来跟这边的前辈学习苏菜的特点
I'm here to learn deeper from other masters of Su cuisine.
# 交流学习主要是来讨教一下
The purpose of this drip is to learn from each other.
# 然后每天会品尝不同层次的美食
And every day I will try a different price level of Su cuisine.
# 我也想看一下就是江苏菜嘛
I'd like to see how different Jiangsu food is.
# 跟我们川菜到底有什么区别
How is it different from our Sichuan cuisine.
# 我们川人喜欢吃麻辣
We Sichuanese like spicy food.
# 然后百菜百味
A hundred dishes will have a hundred flavors.
# 然后这个苏菜正好跟川菜可能有些不一样
Su cuisine is quite different from Sichuan cuisine from what I understand.
# 现在呢我就去先吃
Now I'm going to eat first.
# 然后再跟前辈交流细节 跟前辈讨教
Then we'll exchange our cooking experience with master chefs and ask them for advice on how to deliver authentic Su cuisine.
# 跟前辈学习 好吧我们走吧
Learn from others. All right, let's go.
# 今天吃了很多菜
I had a lot of food today.
# 然后我们现在随便找个酒店住了下来
And now we're checking into a hotel.
# 这个酒店也不算贵 也就100多块钱
This hotel isn't that expensive. It's just over 100 yuan.
# 一个标间我跟我同事一起住
I'm sharing a standard room with my colleague.
# 明天继续
Continue tomorrow.
# 好了
All right.
# 那我们要先去吃个早饭
We're going to have breakfast first.
# 等你们吃完了我这就过来等你们
I'll be right back when you're done.
# 好好好
Okay.
# 这里有三春
Here's the Three Chuns (for breakfast).
# 有富春 冶春 景春
There's Fuchun, Yechun, Jingchun.
# 现在我们去的是什么春啊
Which Chun are we going to now?
# 现在去冶春
Now go to Yechun.
# 冶春
Yechun
# 这个叫什么春
What's this called?
# 治春
Zhi Chun?
# 冶春
Ye Chun
# 我就在这里等你们啊
I'll be right here waiting for you.
# 好的好的
All right, all right.
# 好的 辛苦了 师傅
Okay, thanks, Shifu.
# 没事
It's okay.
# 现在我们已经到了冶春上面了
Now we're here at Yechun.
# 读书少 这个字我第一眼读成治春
I got the character wrong, the first thing I read out is Zhi Chun
# 然后它这个早点不贵
And it's not so expensive for breakfast.
# 跟广东的有点类似 但是品种没有广东那么多
It's similar to Guangdong's, but there aren't as many varieties.
# 就这么一点
That's all.
# 就没有什么了
Not as many.
# 价格也还比较能接受
The price was acceptable.
# 里面包的东西不一样
There's something different in the Bao.
# 好啦 师傅已经在楼下等我们了
Okay, Shifu is waiting for us downstairs.
# 师傅在把这个棚子拉上来
Shifu is pulling this shed up.
# 然后带我们去哪里逛 哪里叫什么
And then you'll show us where to go?
# 乾隆码头 乾隆行宫
Qianlong Pier, Qianlong Palace.
# 八怪名人字画 纪晓岚四库全书
Eight Eccentrics of Yangzhou's Paintings, Ji Xiaolan's Four Siku Quanshu
# 千年老槐树 南柯一梦
A thousand-year-old locust tree, a dream of Nanke.
# 江泽民老家 盐商住宅
Jiang Zemin's old house, Salt trader's residence
# 整个一圈逛下来一个多小时全天导游免费讲解
The whole circle for more than an hour and free guided tour.
# 好的好的 谢谢师傅 那我们现在就走吧
Okay, okay, thank you, Shifu. Let's go now.
# 现在就走
Go now.
# 这里叫什么巷啊师傅
What's the name of this alley, Shifu?
# 驼岭巷
Camelback lane
# 驼岭
Camelback
# 嗯 驼岭巷
Yeah, Camelback Lane.
# 槐树
Locust tree
# 槐树 老槐树
The old locust tree
# 这棵树有多久了
How old is this tree?
# 唐代时期 有1065年
From the Tang Dynasty, it is here for 1065 years.
# 这三棵树给你介绍一下
I'll introduce you to these three trees.
# 好
Good
# 三棵树 是我们扬州的市花 叫琼花
This kind of tree is the city flower of Yangzhou, called Qiong Hua.
# 琼花是我们扬州的市花它叫冰清玉洁
Qiong flower is the city flower of Yangzhou. It's also called "Ice Clear and Jade Clean".
# 今天我们已经来这边好几天了
We've been here for days today.
# 这段时间跟同行跟前辈讨教交流了很多
I've been having a lot of discussions with other cooking masters.
# 也吃了很多
And eat a lot.
# 然后大家可以看一下我现在满脸都是痘痘
And you can see that I'm covered in pimples.
# 胡子也很长
And a messy beard.
# 准备清理一下
I need to get ready to clean up.
# 回去之前再搓一顿
One more meal before we go back.
# 再去吃一下这边的特色
Let's go eat some more specialties here.
# 不会用这个东西
Not good at use this.
# 嗯 果然一点都不痛
Yeah, it didn't hurt at all.
# 如果直接
If use the blade direct
# 干刮的话会很痛
Dry shaving is painful.
# 好了
All right.
# 好 准备走吧
Okay, let's go.